[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "category": "sweetness",
        "question": "How sweet is ",
        "falseAnswers": [ "Very Sweet", "Sweet", "Dry", "Very Dry"]
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "category": "body",
        "question": "How would you describe the body of ",
        "falseAnswers": [ "Full Body", "Medium-full Body", "Medium Body", "Medium-light Body", "Light Body"]
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "category": "tannin",
        "question": "How would you describe the tannin level of ",
        "falseAnswers": [ "High Tannin", "Medium-high Tannin", "Medium Tannin", "Medium-low Tannin", "Low to no Tannin"]
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "category": "acidity",
        "question": "How would you describe the acidity of ",
        "falseAnswers": [ "High Acidity", "Medium-high Acidity", "Medium Acidity", "Medium-low Acidity", "Low Acidity"]
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "category": "alcohol",
        "question": "What is the alcohol by volume of ",
        "falseAnswers": ["10% or less alcohol by volume", "11% Alcohol by volume", "12% Alcohol by volume", "13% Alcohol by volume", "14% Alcohol by volume", "15% or more alcohol by volume"]

    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "category": "temp",
        "question": "At what temperature should you serve ",
        "falseAnswers": [ "38–45°F / 3–7°C", "45–55°F / 7–13°C", "55–60°F / 13–16°C", "Room Temperature"]
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "category": "decant",
        "question": "How long should we decant ",
        "falseAnswers": [ "30 minutes", "1 Hour", "2 Hours", "This wine is not decanted"]
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "category": "ageability",
        "question": "What is the average age for ",
        "falseAnswers": [ "1-3 Years", "3-5 Years", "5-10 Years", "10+ Years"]
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "category": "region",
        "question": "In what region do they make ",
        "falseAnswers": [ "Bordeaux", "Burgundy", "Champagne", "Loire", "Alsace", "Rhône", "Provence", "Languedoc-Roussillon", "Beaujolais", "Jura", "Piedmont", "Tuscany", "Veneto", "Abruzzo", "Sicily", "Napa", "Oregon", "Sonoma", "Washington State", "Port", "Mendoza", " Patagonia", "Bierzo", "Rioja", "Victoria", "Marlborough"]
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "category": "country",
        "question": "In what country do they make ",
        "falseAnswers": ["America", "Australia", "Chile", "England", "France", "Germany", "Hungary", "Italy", "New Zealand", "Spain"]

    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "category": "sparkling",
        "question": "Which accurately describes ",
        "falseAnswers": ["not sparkling", "sparkling"]

    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "category": "color",
        "question": "What color is ",
        "falseAnswers": ["red", "white", "rosè"]

    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "category": "primaryFlavors",
        "question": "Give one of the primary flavors of "
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "category": "varietal",
        "question": "Give one of the grape varietals of "
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "category": "pairings",
        "question": "Give one of the food pairings for "
    }
]